Now it's time for the Ame-challege!
This time
Jenga's Deliberate Defeat Championship
Yay!
Oni ni kuru!
On purpose
Come on!
I'll make you do it!
First of all, there's Jen, who we're all familiar with.
I've rearranged it a little to make it a little more difficult.
First of all, this card...
I can't get it, I can't get it.
I won't do it, I won't do it, I won't do it.
They haven't arrived at all.
I can't do anything because it's not coming out.
I've made it a little harder by reassigning them here.
I'm going to reassign it here to make it a little bit more difficult.
First of all, there is one joker in these cards.
Everyone draws this card, and the person who gets the joker is the one to beat Jenga.
The person who gets the joker's prize intentionally knocks over Jenga.
I see.
So there's one person who isn't genuinely enjoying himself.
So there's a werewolf.
So you have to defeat them without them noticing.
That's right.
We're going to have to take them down.
But not if they find out.
There's a penalty.
I'm sorry.
Well, let's draw cards right away, shall we?
Yes, sir.
Who? Who? Who?
Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
I don't know
I don't get it.
Look again.
I forgot to look at your face.
Like this...
You started it!
That's a start!
One more time.
Ready?
What, what, what, what?
Itchy nose, itchy nose.
I don't know what's wrong with you.
I'm always under suspicion.
I'm under suspicion all the time.
Poor me.
Well, let's get on with it, shall we?
Yes, I'll do it.
Then, let's start Jenga!
It's already Duraradura.
It's going to be durra durra.
It's coming from down here.
And it's coming this way?
This is really it.
They're taking this side all the time.
They're taking this side. They're trying to balance it out.
If you want to keep the balance, and you want the next person to be in the back, you take this side.
But later on, I can do it myself.
Is that so?
You are also putting a lot of effort into it while saying you want to take this side.
I want to take this side and balance it out.
Is it wrong if I take this side?
Is that so?
Thank you for watching.
Is that okay?
You can't use both hands.
Mr. Suzuki uses both hands in Jenga every time.
It's true.
It's okay now that you've said it.
As expected.
You can use both hands there.
Oh, I made a mistake.
I'll take you down a bit.
It's been a while since I've seen someone skating in a love competition.
It's been a while.
What? Why are you stopping here?
Did we stop?
Something stopped.
It's for chocolate.
I got it.
That's good. I see.
Everyone's kind of saying Anpanman all the time in the middle. Hmm.
That's weird. Suspicious.
I'm pretty good at making recommendations, aren't I?
I wonder if I am.
I guess so.
Oh, you're pretty shaky.
Isn't it getting tough? Because it is.
Everywhere looks kind of hard, doesn't it?
The upper part is shaky, so yes.
Don't you like it?
You know, I found a good one.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I'm going to fall over.
Oh, no. What should I do?
Be careful. Crunching.
Ah!
Why are you following me so closely to make me do the crushing?
Oh, is it going to fall down already?
Doubtful, ah, but it's going to fall over.
But it's already going to fall over.
Are you sure you want to follow me?
No, I'm going to fall down already.
I doubt it, aida.
But I'm sure I'm going to fall down.
I've never seen a person who can fly from above like that.
Then, this is the one you just saw.
The one that stopped?
Can you do it?
No, I can't.
I can't do it!
You're not having fun?
There's no more six.
Come on.
Did you try to get them all?
This?
Is this Mr. Ichikawa?
Ichikawa.
Ichikawa
Lo.
Good good good good
Umpire pie.
Tough.
Take it down.
And what's more, it's pretty tilted to begin with.
You want to go that high?
Really?
Oh, my God.
Isn't this kind of weird?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is this possible?
Isn't it a little weird?
The moment you said it was suspicious...
I think I just memorized his face.
I don't want to be here right now.
I really don't.
It's just... well, isn't this kind of weird?
Suspicious.
Oh, my God.
I can't do it.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
No way.
Why now?
But there aren't too many people c-coding at the moment I feel like they're all just regular guys... why not just set them up normally?
I don't care if I'm totally fine. Let's go!
Guess who.
Grace, Plain.
Boo Boo. It's good, isn't it?
dea
Kyu. Yellow.
Congratulations!
Very interesting.
Oh yes, yes, yes!
Janga janga janga janga
I'm trying to do this.
I think it's stopped.
It's not increasing as much as I imagined.
This is the first step.
It's good. It's really good.
It's going to be the other way around.
I'm just gonna take it down like a normal person.
It's gonna be the other way around.
Wait, no, no, no, no, no.
Suzuki.